Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1963-1994, bulk 1985-1993
  - Subject Files, 1964-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accession A2004-28.
    - Keohane, Dr. Nan, 1992 Feb. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - King, Martin Luther: Birthday, 1985 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Knight, Douglas, 1970-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Kreps, Juanita, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Labor Unions, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Langford, Dr. Thomas, 1992 Sept. 1 -1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Language Laboratories, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Latin American Studies, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Law School, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Law School: Site Evaluation, 1992-1993 (Box 100)
    - Law School: Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Law School: Dean Gann, Review of, 1991 Nov. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Law School: Deanship Search, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Leadership Program, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Libraries Advisory Board, University, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Live For Life, 1987 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1986 Feb. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Lord Corporation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Luce Foundation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Academic Plan, 1988 July 1-1988 Dec. 31 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Basic Sciences, Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Center for Living, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Children's Classic, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Children's Hospital Brain Tumor Program, 1992 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Communications, Office Of, 1992 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Community & Family Medicine, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Complaints/Compliments, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Development, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Dolins, Dr. David, 1990 Mar. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Duke University Medical Center: Board of Visitors, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Dupac-Sports Medicine, 1984 July 1-1988 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Eye Center, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Graham, Doyle, Dean of Medical Education, 1987 June 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Health Administration Program, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Health Line, 1986 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Health Policy Research and Education, Center for, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 100)
    - Medical Center: Health Service, Duke, 1985 June 1-1991 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Heart Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Hospital Advisory Board, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Hospital, Duke, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Hospital Bonds, 1985 June 1-1985 Dec. 31 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Howard Hughes Medical Center Institute, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Laszlo, John, 1989 Jan. 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Lenox Baker Hospital, 1987 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Medicine, Department of, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Medicine, School of, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Medpac, 1988 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Miscellaneous, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Nearly New Shoppe, 1985 June 1-1985 July 31 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Nursing, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Private Diagnostic Clinic, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 101)
    - Medical Center: Psychiatry Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Public Relations: Miller, Kay, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Rogers, Mark, Vice Chancellor For Health Affairs, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Sea Level, 1880 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Search For W. G. Anlyan's Replacement, 1987 Dec.-1988 Sept. (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Snyderman, Dr. Ralph: Long Range Plan, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Spicer, Len, 1986 June 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Stockton, Vick, 1990 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Surgery Department, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Vice Chancellor for Health Affairs Candidates, 1992 Oct. 1-1992 Oct. 31 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: VIP Patients, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Wallace, Andrew, 1985 June 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 102)
    - Medical Center: Women's Health Care Advisory Board, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 102)
    - Macronex, 1989 May 1-1989 July 31 (Box 103)
    - Management Board, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Marine Lab, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Marine Lab: Board of Visitors, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Markey Charitable Trust (Lucille), 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Marshall, Roger L., 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Mary Cowper Child Care, Durham Nursery School, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Master of Arts In Liberal Studies (MALS), 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Material Support, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Mathematics Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - McDonald, Eugene (Senior Vice President), 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 103)
    - McDuffie, William, 1986 May 1-1986 Dec. 31 (Box 103)
    - Mellon Foundation, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Meredith, Dennis, 1991 Mar. 1-1993 Dec. 31 (Box 103)
    - Methodist Church: Board Of Higher Education & Ministry, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Methodist Church: Conferences, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Methodist Church: Miscellaneous, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Microelectronics Center of North Carolina (MCNC), 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Middle East Crisis, 1991 Jan. 16-1991 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Mills, Melissa, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Ministry: Campus, 1986 Mar. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Minority Affairs Office, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Mission Statement, University, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Mitsubishi Semiconductor of America, 1986 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Morocco Cooperation Program, 1985 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 103)
    - Morris, Philip, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - Mosbacher Video: Homophobia & Women's Sports, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - Music Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - Nasher, Ray, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges & Universities (NAICU), 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Association of Scholars, 1991 Sept. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Consortium for Educational Access, 1985 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1989 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Foreign Language Resource Center, 1986 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Foundation for Depressive Illness, 1984 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Humanities Center, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Institute of Statistical Sciences, 1990 Sept. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - National Science Foundation, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - Nexus, 1990 July 1-1991 July 31 (Box 104)
    - New York Times, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 104)
    - Nisbet, Caroline: Internship Program, 1991 July 1-1988 June 30 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Association of Colleges & Universities, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - N.C. Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Biotechnology Center, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Board of Science & Technology, 1987 May 1-1987 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Central University, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Friends of Higher Education, 1986 June 1-1986 Dec. 31 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina: Governor Jim Hunt, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina: Governor James G. Martin, 1985 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina National Bank, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State University, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Technology Council, 1985 Nov. 1-1985 Dec. 31 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina, UNC at Chapel Hill, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Northern Telecom, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Olin Foundation, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Ombudsman, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - O'Neil, Liza, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Organizational Charts, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Orientation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Overenrollment, 1986 Jan. 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 105)
    - Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden, 1987 July 1-1988 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Page Auditorium, 1986 Jan. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Parents' Weekend, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Parking, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 105)
    - Patents, 1985 July 1- 1989 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Patent Policy, 1977 Jan. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Personnel, 1985 Jan. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Pew Health Professions Program, 1990 Aug. 1-1990 Aug. 31 (Box 106)
    - Pew Memorial Trust, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Pew Scholars Program, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Pfeiffer College, 1986 Jan. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Pfizer, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1986 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Philanthropy, Center for the Study Of, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Philosophy Department, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Phoenix Communications, Ltd., 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Placement Office, 1982 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Policy, University, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Policy Sciences, Institute of, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Policy Sciences, Institute of: Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Political Correctness, 1992 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Political Science Dept., 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Political Science (Timothy Lomperis), 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Pool Health Trust, 1990 Nov. 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 106)
    - Portraits, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Powell Family, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 106)
    - Presidential Awards, 1992 (Box 107)
    - Presidential Awards, 1991 (Box 107)
    - Presidential Awards, 1990 (Box 107)
    - Presidential Awards Committee, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Presidential Commitments, undated (Box 107)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1992 Feb. 1-1992 Dec. 31 (Box 107)
    - Presidents Of Duke University, 1964 July 1-o (Box 107)
    - President's House, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Preschool & Primary Program, Duke, 1990 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Press, Duke, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Press, Duke: Board of Visitors, 1983 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Price, David, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Price, Reynolds, 1983 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Primate Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Printing Services, 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Private Adjudication Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Proctor and Gamble: Gifts & Grants, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Public Safety, Office of, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Pye, Kenneth, 1987 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Quarter Century Club, 1985 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Questionnaires, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Real Estate, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Recycles, Duke, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Registrar, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Religion Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Research Council, University, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Research Support Office, Duke University, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 107)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1993 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1992 July 1-1992 Dec. 31 (Box 108)
    - Residential College, 1986 Aug. 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 108)
    - Retirement Community, 1991 May 1-1991 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Retrovirus Research Facility, 1985 July 1-1985 Dec. 31 (Box 108)
    - Reynolds Foundation: Gifts & Grants, 1984 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Rich, Rhonda, 1989 May 1-1991 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Rinaldi, Ron, 1987 May 1-1988 June 30 (Box 108)
    - RJR Nabisco, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Robinson, Russell, Charlotte, NC, 1986 Apr. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Romance Languages, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - ROTC: Air Force, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - ROTC: Navy, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Rutherfurd, Jay, 1982 Mar. 1-1985 Dec. 31 (Box 108)
    - Sackler, Dr. Arthur, 1984 Apr. 1-1988 Aug. 30 (Box 108)
    - Safety, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Sanford Distinguished Lectureships, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Scholarships, 1985 July 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 108)
    - Science, Technology & Human Values, Program of, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 108)
    - Segregated Facilities, Use of, 1982 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Senior Class Gift, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Senior Class Party, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Shell Foundation, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Sigma Xi, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Skarulis, Patricia, Vice President for Information Systems, 1989 July 1-1992 Jan.30 (Box 109)
    - Sloan, Alfred P. Foundation, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Small Staff Meetings, 1991 June 1-1992 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Smart Family Foundation, 1985 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Smith, Fred, 1989 June 1-1992 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Smullen, Frank, 1983 June 1-1988 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Sociology Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - South Africa, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - South Atlantic Quarterly, 1986 Jan. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 109)
    - South-East Consortium For International Development (SECID), 1981 Mar. 1-1989 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Southeastern Universities Research Association, Inc. (SURA), 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Southern Association Of Colleges & Schools (SACS), 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Southern Regional Education Board, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Soviet And East European Studies, Center For, 1992 Feb. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Space Planning, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Spangler, R. Patrick, 1981 Jan. 1-1985 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Spanish Studies, The Center for, 1986 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Special Events, Office of, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Spending Rate, 1990 Aug. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 109)
    - Sports Medicine, 1985 Nov. (Box 109)
    - Stanford University, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Starr Foundation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Statistics & Decision Sciences, Institute Of, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Stores Operation, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Student Affairs-Janet Dickerson, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Student Affairs: SALAP/CLAP, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Student Awards, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Students-Deaths, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Students-Health, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Students-Housing, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Students-Letters From Parents, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Students-Miscellaneous, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 110)
    - Students-Miscellaneous (Adam Lynn Film Project), 1991 Feb. 1-1992 Aug. 31 (Box 110)
    - Students-Part-Time Status, 1988 Mar. (Box 111)
    - Students-Problems, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Students-Transfer, 1986 July 1-1989 Sept. 30 (Box 111)
    - Substance Abuse, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Substance Abuse Conference, 1988 Jan. 1-1988 Aug. 31 (Box 111)
    - Sudler, Louis, 1985 Nov. 1-1986 Nov. 30 (Box 111)
    - Suggestion Box, 1991 July 1-1992 Dec. 31 (Box 111)
    - Summer Session, 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Summer Transitional Program, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Surface Science Center, 1987 July 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 111)
    - Talent Identification Program, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Teaching, Masters In, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Technology Transfer Consortium: UNC, NCSU, & Duke, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Technology Transfer Office (Duke), 1987 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Telecommunications, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Thomas, John, 1990 Mar. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 111)
    - TIAA-CREF, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Total Quality Management, 1991 Jan. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Trent, Josiah Charles Memorial Foundation, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Treasurer's Office, 1986 July 1-1986 Aug. 31 (Box 111)
    - Triangle J Council Of Governments, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Triangle Research Libraries Network, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Triangle Universities Computation Center, 1985 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Trinity Board Of Visitors, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 111)
    - Troika, 1986 Apr. 1-1991 Sept. 30 (Box 112)
    - Tuition, 1987 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Undergraduate Judicial Board, 1986 Jan. 1-1987 July 31 (Box 112)
    - Unisys Corporation, 1987 Aug. 1-1990 Sept. 30 (Box 112)
    - United States-Government Agencies-Miscellaneous, 1985 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 112)
    - United States-Miscellaneous, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - United Way, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Universities Research Association, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - University Bylaws, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - University Club, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - University-Government Research, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - University-Industry Relations, 1985 Mar. 1-1986 Dec. 31 (Box 112)
    - University Medal For Distinguished Meritorious Service To The University, 1986 Dec. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - University Relations-David Roberson, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - University Resource Recovery Committee, Duke (URRC), 1989 Feb. 1-1989 Apr. 30 (Box 112)
    - University Union, 1991 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - U.S. Memories, 1989 July 1-1989 Sept. 30 (Box 112)
    - Visitors Center, 1986 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Wadsworth, Dr. Joseph A. C., 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1992 Sept. 1 -1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Washington Duke Hotel, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Weintraub, Prof. Roy, Acting Dean Of The Faculty Of Arts & Sciences, 1993 June (Box 112)
    - Werber, William M., 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Westinghouse, 1985 Aug. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 112)
    - White, Dr. Richard-Dean Of Arts & Sciences, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Whitehead (HMO), 1986 June 1-1991 Aug. 31 (Box 112)
    - Wilder, Pelham, Jr.-University Marshal, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 112)
    - Women Faculty Committee, 1987 July 1-1988 Dec. 31 (Box 113)
    - Women's Studies Program, 1990 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
    - World Environment And Sustainable Development, Center For, 1990 Sept. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
    - World Universities Games, 1988 Sept. 1-1988 Dec. 31 (Box 113)
    - Youth, Center For The Study Of, 1990 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
    - Zoology, Department Of, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
    - Board of Trustees Files, 1985-1993.
      This subseries of the Subject Files series consists of files related to the Duke University Board of Trustees.
      Conditions Governing Access note
      RESTRICTED: Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
      - Trustee Committees: Ad Hoc Committee On The Focus And Priorities Of The Board Of Trustees, 1992 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustee Committees: Ad Hoc Committee To Review The Operations Of The Board, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustee Committees: Investments, 1986 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustee Committees: Medical Center Affairs Subcommittee, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Barnes, Samuel, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Baugh, P. J., 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Bostock, Roy, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Brown, Werner C., 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Caudle, Lloyd, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Chandler, John Wesley, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Cook, Samuel Dubois, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Deane, Disque D., 1987 July 1-1988 Dec. 31 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Donnell, Edward S., 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Drill, Isobel Craven, 1985 July 1-1991 July 31 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Duke, Anthony D., 1985 July 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Esrey, Julie, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Fuqua, J. Rex, 1993 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Garrett, Nathan T., 1985 July 1-1989 July 31 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Grune, George, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Hart, Milledge A., III, 1985 Jan. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Heidrick, Robert L., 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Herbert, George R., 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Holloway, Benjamin, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Hudson, Fitzgerald S., 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Ives, Page H., 1986 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: King, Susan, 1986 Dec. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Kirby, Wallace H., 1986 Apr. 1-1989 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Koskinen, John, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Krauss, Seth D., 1992 Sept. 1 -1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Lane, William, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Levinsohn, Paul A., 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Maisel, David R., 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Mario, Ernest, 1989 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 113)